Kyaw Soe Win

Personal Detail

Address

No (20) Building B 6th floor, Zalun Street, Sanchaung Township, Yangon

Phone

09459092375

E-mail

kyawsoewin.august@gmail.com

Date of birth

29.08.1994

Skills

- Android
- Java
- JSON
- SOL Fundamentals
- UML
- Project Management
- SDLC
- Kotlin

Certificate

• Project Management (Executive Institute Academy)

Strength

- Team Player
- Problem Solving
- Fast Learner

Language

English



CAREER OBJECTIVE

To work as a professional developer in an organization where I can utilize my skills and knowledge related to develop robust applications.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Known for writing efficient, maintainable and reusable code
- Experienced in interaction between various devices and version of Android
- Strong knowledge of Android SDK, different versions of Android and how to deal with different screen sizes
- Experienced in code versioning tools and release systems such as Git
- Familiarity with RESTful APIs to connect Android applications to back-end services
- Strong knowledge of Android UI design principles and patterns
- Knowledge of agile SCRUM, Git and Atlassian toolset
- Experience with Unit Testing
- Experience with 2D charting
- Familiarity with cloud message APIs and push notifications
- Experience with VOIP Integration

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Science and Technology (2016) Yadanarpon Cyber City, Mandalay

ABOUT ME

Graduated from Yadanarpon Cyber City (YCC). After graduated, I started internship at 72 Coder Company about one month. I made one freelance project during one week. I worked as Junior Android Developer at Trustinno Company. I have not only technology knowledge but also project management knowledge. I am worked as Junior Solution Architect at MyanCare Company. I work as freelancer too.

EXPERIENCE

72 Coder Company

Internship Android Developer (5/05/2017 – 31/05/2017)

Mobile Doctor

- Develop application using java
- Testing Application

Trustinno Company

Junior Android Developer (7/06/2017 - 31/03/2018) Jobready365

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use SQLite for storage
- Use Glide Library for loading Photo
- Use Git for development

MyanmarInfoCenter

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use Picasso Library for loading Photo
- Develop application with MVP Architecture
- Use Git for development

MyanmarJobCenter

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Develop application with MVP Architecture
- Use Git for development
- Integrate with firebase for push notification

MyanCare Company

Junior Android Developer (1/04/2018 – 6/12/2018)

MyanCare/MyanCare Doctor

- Requirement Analysis
- Report Daily Project Status
- System Analysis
- Protyping Application
- Analysis Source Code
- Use Git for development
- Develop Application with high code quality
- Integrate VOIP service

Justlogin Company

Android Developer (25/04/2019 – Current)

Justlogin Mobile/Justlogin Kiosk/Just Login MECS

- Report Daily Project Status
- Use Git for development
- Develop Application with high code quality
- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Integrate with FCM for push notification
- Integrate with Firebase Remote Config/Crashlytics/Analysis